

Leonardo Diesel

← +353 89 988 9156 diesel.leonardo@gmail.com

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/leonardo-diesel/

https://dieselcct.github.io/my_portfolio/

Summary

Having been an IT professional with nearly a decade of experience in desktop support, I bring a wealth of technical experiences in AWS, Google Cloud, Active Directory, Microsoft Office 365 in and programming languages including Java, JavaScript, Python, Flutter, SpringBoot, NodeJS, CSS and HTML. I am a dedicated and curious individual eager to apply problem solving, productivity, stress resistance, critical, and analytical thinking to a dynamic environment opportunity. With extensive and different experiences, my commitment to learning and adaptability is evident throughout my career. Native Portuguese speaker and with high English fluency, I am also an intermediate speaker in French and Spanish, and beginner at German. Outside the IT realm, my diverse skill set extends to gaming, financial trends, football, running, and guitar playing.

Education

CCT COLLEGE DUBLIN - Dublin, Ireland

September 2020 – June 2024 (Expected)

B.S.(Hons) in Computer Science & Information Technology

Modules: Professional Development, Cloud Services, Artificial Intelligence, Data Visualisation & Communication, Data Exploration & Preparation, Concurrent Systems, Commercial Solutions Design, Network & System Security, Algorithms, Architecture & Design Patterns, Integrated Application Development, Legal, Ethical & Privacy Issues, Adv. Numerical Methods, Distributed Digital Transactions, Cross-Platform Development, Databases: Approaches & Systems, Network Services & Virtualisation, Business Information Systems, Research Skills, Wireless Networking and Switching & Routing.

Technical Skills

- Programming: Java, JavaScript, Python, Flutter, SpringBoot, NodeJS
- Cloud: AWS and Google Cloud Platform
- Databases: Firebird, MySQL and MongoDB
- Networking: Cisco Packet Tracer, WireShark, VLAN, Troubleshooting and Network Configuration
- Hardware: Printers, PC Assembly and Troubleshooting
- Operating Systems: Windows and Linux
- Support: Active Directory, Microsoft Office 365, Windows Administration and Server, ERP, and System Configuration.

Working Experience

Mulligan and Haines - Dublin, Ireland Supervisor

May 2022 - present

- Ensured smooth day-to-day bar operations
- Maintained a safe and enjoyable customer environment
- Conducted end-of-day cash reconciliation with a focus on accuracy
- Trained floor and bar employees
- Full compliance with health, safety, and hygiene standards

Badass Cafe - Dublin, Ireland

August 2019 - April 2022

Bartender

- Floor staff and bartender
- Stock management
- Full compliance with health, safety, and hygiene standards.

KFC - Dublin, Ireland

July 2018 - August 2019

Chef

- Preparing and cooking items in a fast-paced and hectic environment
- Ensuring Health and Safety guidelines are followed at all times

Grosvenor Group - Dublin, Ireland

April 2018 - October 2018

Cleaner

- Ensuring the workplace is clean and tidy for the day and the following working day
- Use of electrical equipment in a safe and effective manner

Office System Informatica LTDA - Lajeado, Brazil

August 2008 - September 2017

- **Desktop Support Specialist**
 - Software support to direct customers through phone calls, skype, chat, msn and remote access
 - Software support to software resellers and partners through phone calls, skype, chat, msn and remote
 - Customer data management (Firebird)
 - Analyse, measure and document customer's demands

Caixa Economica Federal (Bank) - Estrela, Brazil

January 2008 - July 2008

Intern/Office Assistant

- Customer support: handle complaints and technical issues
- Data transcription of the clients within the online banking system
- Account opening for new clients